<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><!-- no stylesheet -->
<provisional>
	<arrive>2013-10-01</arrive>
	<checkin>2013-10-01</checkin>
	<checkout>2013-10-15</checkout>
	<currency>ZAR</currency>
	<depart>2013-10-15</depart>
	<deposit>0.0</deposit>
	<emailaddress>tim@pinaway.com</emailaddress>
	<familyname>Martin</familyname>
	<firstname>Tim</firstname>
	<message>The provisional reservation number is 119157</message>
	<notes>Honeymoon couple!</notes>
	<productid>145</productid>
	<productname>Camps Bay Terrace Penthouse</productname>
	<quote>41905.0</quote>
	<rack>46200.0</rack>
	<reservationid>765090</reservationid>
	<reservationname>119157</reservationname>
	<sto>41905.0</sto>
	<terms>Please contact us if we can help in any way. We arrange
		airport transfers, car hire, tours, restaurant bookings or anything
		else to make your stay with us enjoyable. Also let us know of any
		particular requirements such as cots and high chairs for infants. We
		can also happily pre-stock your apartment with food and drinks on your
		behalf. If you will be celebrating a special occasion during your
		stay such as a birthday, anniversary or honeymoon, please let us know
		so that we can make that extra effort on your special day.

		Arrival and Departure
		Check-in time is between 14h00 and 18h00 unless otherwise arranged. Check-out
		time is before 11h00 on the day of departure. We try to accommodate
		other arrival and departure times, so if you have any special
		requests please let us know. Please contact 45 minutes prior to your
		arrival at the property on +27 21 438 6440 during office hours, or on
		+27 84 804 9902 after hours. Please be aware that there is an
		after-hours arrival charge of R300 for any arrivals between 19h00 and
		7h00.

		Passports
		South African immigration laws require all visitors' passports to have at
		least two blank pages and to be valid at least six months from
		your planned date of departure from South Africa. The law is
		rigorously enforced so please check your passports without delay!

		Cancellations
		Bookings cancelled more than 90 days prior to arrival date pay a 10%
		cancellation fee.
		Bookings cancelled between 90 and 61 days of arrival date pay a 25%
		cancellation fee.
		Bookings cancelled between 60 and 31 days of arrival date pay a 50%
		cancellation fee.
		Bookings cancelled less than 30 days from arrival date pay a 100% cancellation
		fee.

		Refunds and waiver of cancellation policies are at the discretion
		of management and their ability to relet the room. We advise all
		clients to take out cancellation insurance.

		All changes to bookings once confirmed, including moving from one
		property to another, or amending dates, are deemed to be cancellation
		of the first booking, and applicable fees must be charged.

		Terms and Conditions
		Please go to http://www.noxrentals.co.za/uploads/rentalagreement.pdf for
		our full terms and conditions of contract. Your deposit is deemed to
		be acceptance of the said terms and conditions. No binding
		contract is in force until such time as a rental deposit has been
		made, and the rental manager has vetted and accepted the payment and
		guest information, and communicated such to the client.

		BANK DETAILS:
		NAME: NOX TOURISM
		BANK: NEDBANK
		ACCOUNT NUMBER: 1232064025
		BRANCH CODE: 123209
		BRANCH: BUSINESS SOUTHERN PENINSULA
		SWIFT: NEDSZAJJ
	</terms>
	<xsl>'no_xsl'</xsl>
</provisional>
